{"sid": "3IQM90OT5B6C_main", "calc_equals_delay": 3, "block_data": {"block_0": {"mean_level": 8, "start_time": 338138, "questions": {"q0": {"time_left_start": "300", "question_time_start": 338140, "question": "78+37+23+47", "correct_answer": 185, "events": [["submit", 374189]], "time_left_end": "264", "answered_time": 374189, "user_answer": "185", "user_correct": "True", "score": "1"}, "q1": {"time_left_start": "264", "question_time_start": 374190, "question": "4+3+6+13", "correct_answer": 26, "events": [["submit", 379147]], "time_left_end": "259", "answered_time": 379147, "user_answer": "26", "user_correct": "True", "score": "2"}, "q2": {"time_left_start": "259", "question_time_start": 379147, "question": "4+24+17", "correct_answer": 45, "events": [["submit", 384284]], "time_left_end": "254", "answered_time": 384284, "user_answer": "45", "user_correct": "True", "score": "3"}, "q3": {"time_left_start": "254", "question_time_start": 384285, "question": "6+7+7+43", "correct_answer": 63, "events": [["submit", 389786]], "time_left_end": "249", "answered_time": 389786, "user_answer": "63", "user_correct": "True", "score": "4"}, "q4": {"time_left_start": "249", "question_time_start": 389786, "question": "34+873", "correct_answer": 907, "events": [["submit", 401024]], "time_left_end": "238", "answered_time": 401024, "user_answer": "907", "user_correct": "True", "score": "5"}, "q5": {"time_left_start": "238", "question_time_start": 401025, "question": "7+68+83", "correct_answer": 158, "events": [["submit", 410937]], "time_left_end": "228", "answered_time": 410937, "user_answer": "158", "user_correct": "True", "score": "6"}, "q6": {"time_left_start": "228", "question_time_start": 410937, "question": "8+98+77", "correct_answer": 183, "events": [["submit", 418832]], "time_left_end": "220", "answered_time": 418832, "user_answer": "183", "user_correct": "True", "score": "7"}, "q7": {"time_left_start": "220", "question_time_start": 418833, "question": "24+516", "correct_answer": 540, "events": [["submit", 425147]], "time_left_end": "213", "answered_time": 425147, "user_answer": "540", "user_correct": "True", "score": "8"}, "q8": {"time_left_start": "213", "question_time_start": 425147, "question": "63+13", "correct_answer": 76, "events": [["submit", 427865]], "time_left_end": "211", "answered_time": 427865, "user_answer": "76", "user_correct": "True", "score": "9"}, "q9": {"time_left_start": "211", "question_time_start": 427865, "question": "19+86", "correct_answer": 105, "events": [["submit", 430883]], "time_left_end": "208", "answered_time": 430883, "user_answer": "105", "user_correct": "True", "score": "10"}}}, "block_1": {"mean_level": 8, "start_time": 430883, "questions": {"q0": {"time_left_start": "208", "question_time_start": 430883, "question": "8+14+93", "correct_answer": 115, "events": [["submit", 440421]], "time_left_end": "198", "answered_time": 440421, "user_answer": "115", "user_correct": "True", "score": "11"}, "q1": {"time_left_start": "198", "question_time_start": 440421, "question": "34+319", "correct_answer": 353, "events": [["submit", 445945]], "time_left_end": "193", "answered_time": 445945, "user_answer": "353", "user_correct": "True", "score": "12"}, "q2": {"time_left_start": "193", "question_time_start": 445945, "question": "6+37+46", "correct_answer": 89, "events": [["submit", 452415]], "time_left_end": "186", "answered_time": 452415, "user_answer": "89", "user_correct": "True", "score": "13"}, "q3": {"time_left_start": "186", "question_time_start": 452416, "question": "57+33", "correct_answer": 90, "events": [["submit", 455261]], "time_left_end": "183", "answered_time": 455261, "user_answer": "90", "user_correct": "True", "score": "14"}, "q4": {"time_left_start": "183", "question_time_start": 455261, "question": "4+6+4+53", "correct_answer": 67, "events": [["submit", 460230]], "time_left_end": "178", "answered_time": 460230, "user_answer": "67", "user_correct": "True", "score": "15"}, "q5": {"time_left_start": "178", "question_time_start": 460230, "question": "77+984", "correct_answer": 1061, "events": [["submit", 473302]], "time_left_end": "165", "answered_time": 473302, "user_answer": "1061", "user_correct": "True", "score": "16"}, "q6": {"time_left_start": "165", "question_time_start": 473303, "question": "63+58+74+43", "correct_answer": 238, "events": [["submit", 495024]], "time_left_end": "144", "answered_time": 495024, "user_answer": "238", "user_correct": "True", "score": "17"}, "q7": {"time_left_start": "144", "question_time_start": 495024, "question": "7+9+8+28", "correct_answer": 52, "events": [["submit", 502520]], "time_left_end": "136", "answered_time": 502520, "user_answer": "52", "user_correct": "True", "score": "18"}, "q8": {"time_left_start": "136", "question_time_start": 502521, "question": "9+27+68", "correct_answer": 104, "events": [["submit", 512864]], "time_left_end": "126", "answered_time": 512864, "user_answer": "104", "user_correct": "True", "score": "19"}, "q9": {"time_left_start": "126", "question_time_start": 512864, "question": "53+99", "correct_answer": 152, "events": [["submit", 515528]], "time_left_end": "123", "answered_time": 515528, "user_answer": "152", "user_correct": "True", "score": "20"}}}, "block_2": {"mean_level": 8, "start_time": 515528, "questions": {"q0": {"time_left_start": "123", "question_time_start": 515528, "question": "93+54+47+48", "correct_answer": 242, "events": [["submit", 538383]], "time_left_end": "100", "answered_time": 538383, "user_answer": "242", "user_correct": "True", "score": "21"}, "q1": {"time_left_start": "100", "question_time_start": 538384, "question": "9+26+54", "correct_answer": 89, "events": [["submit", 545620]], "time_left_end": "93", "answered_time": 545620, "user_answer": "89", "user_correct": "True", "score": "22"}, "q2": {"time_left_start": "93", "question_time_start": 545621, "question": "87+133", "correct_answer": 220, "events": [["submit", 553857]], "time_left_end": "85", "answered_time": 553857, "user_answer": "210", "user_correct": "False", "score": "21"}, "q3": {"time_left_start": "85", "question_time_start": 553858, "question": "9+8+8+36", "correct_answer": 61, "events": [["submit", 564841]], "time_left_end": "74", "answered_time": 564841, "user_answer": "61", "user_correct": "True", "score": "22"}, "q4": {"time_left_start": "74", "question_time_start": 564841, "question": "6+8+3+16", "correct_answer": 33, "events": [["submit", 571464]], "time_left_end": "67", "answered_time": 571464, "user_answer": "33", "user_correct": "True", "score": "23"}, "q5": {"time_left_start": "67", "question_time_start": 571464, "question": "27+777", "correct_answer": 804, "events": [["submit", 578316]], "time_left_end": "60", "answered_time": 578316, "user_answer": "804", "user_correct": "True", "score": "24"}, "q6": {"time_left_start": "60", "question_time_start": 578316, "question": "7+67+98", "correct_answer": 172, "events": [["submit", 585765]], "time_left_end": "53", "answered_time": 585765, "user_answer": "172", "user_correct": "True", "score": "25"}, "q7": {"time_left_start": "53", "question_time_start": 585765, "question": "3+33+87", "correct_answer": 123, "events": [["submit", 597702]], "time_left_end": "41", "answered_time": 597702, "user_answer": "123", "user_correct": "True", "score": "26"}, "q8": {"time_left_start": "41", "question_time_start": 597702, "question": "46+99", "correct_answer": 145, "events": [["submit", 600304]], "time_left_end": "38", "answered_time": 600304, "user_answer": "145", "user_correct": "True", "score": "27"}, "q9": {"time_left_start": "38", "question_time_start": 600304, "question": "28+67", "correct_answer": 95, "events": [["submit", 605129]], "time_left_end": "33", "answered_time": 605129, "user_answer": "95", "user_correct": "True", "score": "28"}}}, "block_3": {"mean_level": 8, "start_time": 605129, "questions": {"q0": {"time_left_start": "33", "question_time_start": 605129, "question": "83+36", "correct_answer": 119, "events": [["submit", 610797]], "time_left_end": "28", "answered_time": 610797, "user_answer": "109", "user_correct": "False", "score": "27"}, "q1": {"time_left_start": "28", "question_time_start": 610797, "question": "8+97+44", "correct_answer": 149, "events": [["submit", 619404]], "time_left_end": "19", "answered_time": 619404, "user_answer": "149", "user_correct": "True", "score": "28"}, "q2": {"time_left_start": "19", "question_time_start": 619405, "question": "6+4+3+58", "correct_answer": 71, "events": [["submit", 624510]], "time_left_end": "14", "answered_time": 624510, "user_answer": "71", "user_correct": "True", "score": "29"}, "q3": {"time_left_start": "14", "question_time_start": 624510, "question": "6+4+8+49", "correct_answer": 67, "events": [["submit", 630037]], "time_left_end": "9", "answered_time": 630037, "user_answer": "67", "user_correct": "True", "score": "30"}, "q4": {"time_left_start": "9", "question_time_start": 630037, "question": "7+96+99", "correct_answer": 202, "events": [["submit", 635251]], "time_left_end": "3", "answered_time": 635251, "user_answer": "202", "user_correct": "True", "score": "31"}, "q5": {"time_left_start": "3", "question_time_start": 635251, "question": "53+83+18+78", "correct_answer": 232, "events": []}}}}}